Guide to the Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records, 1972-2009.
Parents, Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG) records
- Series IX. Audiocassettes and Videocassettes
  - 1995 P-FLAG Convention, Indianapolis, IN 30 September - 1 October
    - The Massachusetts Project: Making Schools Safe for Gay and Lesbian Youth (Box 15, Folder 95-P26)
    - Missing (Box 15, Folder 95-P27)
    - Teens Tell Their Own Stories (Box 15, Folder 95-P28)
    - Bisexuality - Addressing the Myths (Box 15, Folder 95-P29)
    - Liberty and Justice for All (Box 15, Folder 95-P30)
    - The Coming Out Experience for Children of Lesbians, Gays, and Bisexuals (Box 15, Folder 95-P31)
    - Gay Genes: Homosexuality and Biology (Box 15, Folder 95-P32)
    - Missing (Box 15, Folder 95-P33)
    - Missing (Box 15, Folder 95-P34)
    - Missing (Box 15, Folder 95-P35)
    - Crossing Point: P-FLAG and the Gay Movement Make History (Box 15, Folder 95-P36)
    - Missing (Box 15, Folder 95-P37)
    - P-FLAG and AIDS: The Personal Side (Box 15, Folder 95-P38)
    - Missing (Box 15, Folder 95-P39)
    - The Values of Family: Positive Image of Gays and Lesbians (Box 15, Folder 95-P40)
    - Gays and Lesbians in the Workplace: Creating a Tolerant Environment (Box 15, Folder 95-P41)
    - Missing (Box 15, Folder 95-P42)
    - Freedom to Marry: Re-educating America to Build Support for the Freedom to Marry (Box 15, Folder 95-P43)
    - The Challenges and Opportunities in 1996 for Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgendered Youth (Box 15, Folder 95-P44)
    - Keynote Address: Mel White (Box 15, Folder 95-P45)
    - 1995 P-FLAG Leadership Training Institute, 29 September
    - Leadership Training Institute (Box 15, Folder 95-LTI-1)
    - Leadership Training Institute (Box 15, Folder 95-LTI-2)
    - Leadership Training Institute (Box 15, Folder 95-LTI-3)
    - Leadership Training Institute (Box 15, Folder 95-LTI-4)
  - 1996 P-FLAG Convention, Washington, DC, 11-14 October
    - Opening Plenary Session: 15 Years of Love Taking Action (two tapes) (Box 16, Folder FF)
    - Why and How Schools Need to Address Issues of Sexual Orientation - missing (Box 14, Folder 96-1)
    - Smoke and Mirrors: Federal Legislative Update - missing (Box 14, Folder 96-2)
    - Advocating for Equality in Our Houses of Worship (Box 14, Folder 96-3)
    - It's Not Just a Phase: Defending Sexual Minority Youth Issues (Box 14, Folder 96-4)
    - Note: tape 96-5 does not exist
    - Media Relations 101 (Box 14, Folder 96-6)
    - Marriage 101: Why Marriage Matters - missing (Box 14, Folder 96-7)
    - Internalized Homophobia: Putting It on the Table (Box 14, Folder 96-8)
    - Beyond Bi-101: Who We Are and What We Stand For (Box 14, Folder 96-9)
    - Note: tape 96-10 does not exist (Box 14, Folder 96-10)
    - Setting Up Your Chapter's Help-Hotline/Referral Training (Box 14, Folder 96-11)
    - P-FLAG: 15 Years (Box 14, Folder 96-12)
    - Managing a Chapter: Leading, Delegating and Moving Forward Together (two tapes) (Box 14, Folder 96-13)
    - Conflict Mediation and Interpersonal Management (two tapes) (Box 14, Folder 96-14)
    - Fundraising for Your Chapter Made Easy (two tapes) (Box 14, Folder 96-15)
    - Making Schools Safe for Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Youth - missing (Box 14, Folder 96-16)
    - Moving Your Congress-person Toward Fairness: The Basics of Lobbying (Box 14, Folder 96-17)
    - Biblical Self-Defense (Box 14, Folder 96-18)
    - Note: tape 96-19 does not exist (Box 14, Folder 96-19)
    - Media Relations 102 (Box 14, Folder 96-20)
    - Marriage 102: How to Do Public Education and Outreach (Box 14, Folder 96-21)
    - Visibility Issues for Families (Box 14, Folder 96-22)
    - Supporting Families and Friends of Transgendered People (Box 14, Folder 96-23)
    - Rural Organizing: Dealing with Population, Members and Money (Box 14, Folder 96-24)
    - Note: tape 96-25 does not exist (Box 14, Folder 96-25)
    - Using the Internet 5 Different Ways: Support, Education, Advocacy, Personal and Chapter Development (Box 14, Folder 96-26)
    - Get the Connection? Sexuality and Health Education Under Attack (Box 14, Folder 96-27)
    - It's Elementary: Including Gay Issues in Early Education (Box 14, Folder 96-28)
    - Federal HIV/AIDS Related Policy and Legislation (Box 14, Folder 96-29)
    - Coalition Building: Reaching Interfaith Communities (Box 14, Folder 96-30)
    - Creating Social/Support Groups for Lesbian/Gay/Bisexual Youth (Box 14, Folder 96-31)
    - Note: tape 96-32 does not exist (Box 14, Folder 96-32)
    - Speaking in Public - missing (Box 14, Folder 96-33)
    - How to Win at the State Level (Box 14, Folder 96-34)
    - Family Values: Lesbian and Gay Parents and Their Children (Box 14, Folder 96-35)
    - Supporting Caregivers of Loved Ones with AIDS (Box 14, Folder 96-36)
    - Skills and Strategies: Opening Corporate America to P-FLAG II (Box 14, Folder 96-37)
    - How to Stop Witch Hunts Against Our Family in the Military (Box 14, Folder 96-38)
    - State Councils: Taking the Next Step to Organizing (Box 14, Folder 96-39)
    - Membership: Motivating and Activating Members (two tapes) (Box 14, Folder 96-40)
    - Note: tape 96-41 does not exist (Box 14, Folder 96-41)
    - Project Open Mind (two tapes) (Box 14, Folder 96-42)
    - How Well Do You Know Your School Board? (Box 14, Folder 96-43)
    - Inside Politics 1996 (Box 14, Folder 96-44)
    - Sexual Minority Youth in High-Risk Situations: Research Overview and Model Programs (Box 14, Folder 96-45)
    - Asian Pacific Islanders P-FLAG Family Project (Box 14, Folder 96-46)
    - How to Stay Calm and Be Effective in a Hostile Climate (Box 14, Folder 96-47)
    - Note: tape 96-48 does not exist (Box 14, Folder 96-48)
    - Supporting Straight Spouses (Box 14, Folder 96-49)
    - Policing the Gay Community: Bridging the Gap (Box 14, Folder 96-50)
    - Winning Against the Radical Right (Box 14, Folder 96-51)
    - Organizing Conferences, Seminars and Workshops (Box 14, Folder 96-52)
    - A True Friend: Welcoming Friends in the P-FLAG Community (Box 14, Folder 96-53)
    - Instruments of Change: Building Bridges Between Sexual Minorities and Communities of Color (Box 14, Folder 96-54)
    - Interfaith Celebration (Box 16, Folder GG)
    - 1996 P-FLAG Leadership Training Institute, 11 October
    - Institute I: Chapter Fundraising (four tapes) (Box 14, Folder 96-AA)
    - Institute II: Project Open Mind - The Basics of Running a Public Education Campaign (four tapes) (Box 16, Folder 96-BB)
    - Institute III: Advocating for Sexual Minority Youth in Schools (four tapes) (Box 16, Folder 96-CC)
    - Note: tape 96-DD does not exist (Box 16, Folder 96-DD)
    - Leadership Training Institutes Luncheon (Box 16, Folder 96-EE)
      Dot Ridings, Council on Foundation
    - 1997 P-FLAG National Convention, Orlando, FL, 11-14 September
    - Leadership Training Institute Luncheon: Guest Speaker: Ethel Klein (Box 65, Folder tr8671a)
    - PLFAG Conference '97 Kick-Off - Tape 1 (Box 65, Folder tr8672a)
    - PFLAG Conference '97 Kick-Off - Tape 2 (Box 65, Folder tr8673a)
    - President to President: Sharing Our Vision for the Coming Year (Box 65, Folder tr8674a)
    - PFLAG and Youth: Elements of Successful Programming (Box 65, Folder tr8675a)
    - Culturally Competent PFLAG (Box 65, Folder tr8676a)
    - Issues for 1998 and Beyond: federal Legislative Update (Box 65, Folder tr8677a)
    - Bisexuality: Building Community at the Local and National Level (Box 65, Folder tr8678a)
    - Understanding the Needs of Families of Transgender People (Box 65, Folder tr8679a)
    - Interfaith Organizing: Strategic Organizing for PFLAG Members and Leaders (Box 65, Folder tr8680a)
    - Current Medical Breakthroughs: What Concerned Families Should Know (Box 65, Folder tr8681a)
    - Addressing the Needs of Straight Spouses (Box 65, Folder tr8682a)
    - Chapter Awards Luncheon: Speaker: Ted Childs (Box 65, Folder tr8683a)
    - Strategic/Annual Planning for PFLAG Chapters - Tape 1 (Box 65, Folder tr8684a)
    - Strategic/Annual Planning for PFLAG Chapters - Tape 2 (Box 65, Folder tr8685a)
    - Conducting a Public Education Campaign/Program Open Mind - Tape 1 (Box 65, Folder tr8686a)
    - Conducting a Public Education Campaign/Program Open Mind - Tape 2 (Box 65, Folder tr8687a)
    - Supporting Families and Friends of Transgender People (Box 65, Folder tr8688a)
    - Safe Schools: Addressing and Meeting the Critical Needs (Box 65, Folder tr8689a)
    - Corporate Workplace Equality: Progress and Prospects (Box 65, Folder tr8690a)
    - Advocating for Equal Rights as a PFLAG Member (Box 65, Folder tr8691a)
    - Model PFLAG Support Meeting (Box 65, Folder tr8692a)
    - Bringing Faith Communities to Inclusiveness (Box 65, Folder tr8693a)
    - Protecting All Families: The Work to Secure Same-Gender Marriage (Box 65, Folder tr8694a)
    - The Good, The Bad and The Ugly: Progressive and Punitive Education Policies (Box 65, Folder tr8695a)
    - Gay-Friendly Workplaces: How to Find and/or Create Them (Box 65, Folder tr8696a)
    - Membership Development: Offering Opportunities Always (Box 65, Folder tr8697a)
    - Stopping Anti-Gay Abuse of Students in Public Schools (Box 65, Folder tr8698a)
    - Wake-Up Call: Using Drama to Create Safe Space for All Students (Box 65, Folder tr8699a)
    - When You Are "Out" More Than Your Child (Box 65, Folder tr8700a)
    - Personal Reconciliation With Your Faith Community (Box 65, Folder tr8701a)
    - Ex-Ex: A Personal Look at the "Ex-Gay" Movement (Box 65, Folder tr8702a)
    - Supporting Support: Basic and Advance Support Group Facilitation (Box 65, Folder tr8703a)
    - Finding Your Voice: Learning to Lead - Tape 1 (Box 65, Folder tr8704a)
    - Finding Your Voice: Learning to Lead - Tape 2 (Box 65, Folder tr8705a)
    - Coming Out: A Personal Journey of Discovery (Box 65, Folder tr8706a)
    - Building Resources for Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Youth and Their Families in Rural Communities (Box 65, Folder tr8707a)
    - Working Together to Achieve Our Common Goals: Partnerships Between PFLAG's National and Local Leaders (Box 65, Folder tr8708a)
    - Challenges of Organizing in Southern States (Box 65, Folder tr8709a)
    - Media Essentials Training (Box 65, Folder tr8710a)
    - How PFLAGers Bring in Resources (Box 65, Folder tr8711a)
    - Beyond "Don't Ask, Don't Tell": Current Military Practices (Box 65, Folder tr8712a)
    - Safe Space for Sexual Minority Youth: Support Groups and Other Programs (Box 65, Folder tr8713a)
    - Conflict Mediation and Interpersonal Management (Box 65, Folder tr8714a)
    - Health Care Needs of Sexual Minorities (Box 65, Folder tr8715a)
    - Organizing a Speakers Bureau (Box 65, Folder tr8716a)
    - Media Presence Training (Box 65, Folder tr8717a)
    - A True Friend: Welcoming Friends Into the PFLAG Family (Box 65, Folder tr8718a)
    - Overcoming Prejudice: Skills for Working Through Differences (Box 65, Folder tr8719a)
    - Youth and Adults Working Together: Building Effective Partnerships (Box 65, Folder tr8720a)
    - How to Avoid a Burn-Out (Box 65, Folder tr8721a)
    - Parkas and Polar Bears: What Are Canadian PFLAGers All About? (Box 65, Folder tr8722a)
    - PFLAG On the Air: Accessing Community Television (Box 65, Folder tr8723a)
    - Bring PFLAG Planned Giving Financial Seminars To Your Area (Box 65, Folder tr8724a)
    - PFLAG Annual Meeting - Tape 1 (Box 65, Folder tr8725a)
    - PFLAG Annual Meeting - Tape 2 (Box 65, Folder tr8726a)
  - 1997 P-FLAG Leadership Training Institute, Orlando, FL, 12 September: Creating Safe Space for Sexual Minority Youth in Schools
    - Section I: Stopping Anti-Gay Abuse in Schools: A Legal Framework (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Section II: Speaker Training (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Section III: Conducting Training (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Section IV: Policy (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Section V: Safe Schools Coalitions (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Section VI: Fact Sheets and Articles (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Section VII: Resources (Box 67, Folder 45)
  - Queens Lesbian and Gay Pride: Speeches by Jeanne Manford and Judge Karen Bursten - Dante's, February 4, 1995; tr8727a (Box 65)
  - Liza Minnelli, "The Day After That"--benefit tape for AmFAR, 1993; tr.8113a (Box 62)
  - [unlabeled], tr.8114a (Box 62)
  - Ken Markmer, tr.8115a (Box 62)
  - PFLAG--Lobby Workshop, Apr. 17, 1993; tr.8116a (Box 62)
  - This Way Out, Apr. 23, 2001; tr.8117a (Box 62)
  - This Way Out, Apr. 16, 2001; tr.8118a (Box 62)
  - Mitzi Henderson--WAVA, tr.8119a (Box 62)
  - Michael W. Gilboe, Composition Demo, tr.8120a (Box 62)
  - 11:15AM, Feb. 27, 1999; tr.8121a (Box 62)
  - 8:30 AM, Nov. 7, 1998; tr.8122a (Box 62)
  - The Uppity Women Hour: Peggy Gage, PFLAG NH Seacoast, Squaring PFLAG with the GOP, tr.8123a (Box 62)
  - Prime Time Radio: Helping Families Cope with Homosexuality, March 1, 1994; tr.8124a (Box 62)
  - William Beale and Mike Neubecker, LesBiGay radio, Fathers' Day 2000, June 16, 2000; tr.8125a (Box 62)
  - Kurt Olson, Kim Campbell, tr.8126a (Box 62)
  - Anti-gay interview with former homosexual Michael Johnson, Oct. 10, 1995; tr.8127a (Box 62)
  - PFLAG Bellingham, interview talk show, the Bonnie Lou Show, Oct. 9, 1995; tr.8128a (Box 62)
  - Gays in Military free speech message, June 1993; tr.8129a (Box 62)
  - B. Oxman, PFLAG interview, Dec. 14, 1993; tr.8130a (Box 62)
  - PFLAG PSA, tr.8131 (Box 62)
  - Lesbian and Gay Entrepreneurs--Denver Parents FLAG, Jul. 6, 1994; tr.8132a (Box 62)
  - A Tribute to the Memory of You by Denny Hamann, 1989; tr.8133a (Box 60)
  - PFLAG--J. Garrett, tr.8134a (Box 60)
  - PFLAG--J. Garrett, May 16, 1996; tr.8135a (Box 60)
  - Interview--Jerry and Cherie Garland, Sound Recording--Los Angeles Gay Men's Chorus, tr.8136a (Box 60)
  - PFFAG Lynette and Larry, tr.8137a (Box 60)
  - Kim Campbell, Francine Helfman, tr.8138a (Box 60)
  - [unlabeled], tr.8139a (Box 60)
  - Dave Berkman--Support for Gays, Lesbians, and Bi-sexuals--Mitzi Henderson, Jul. 18, 1994; tr.8140a (Box 60)
  - Mike and Jan Neubecker on "Christian" Talk Radio--PFLAG Downriver, tr.8141a (Box 60)
  - Thomas-Kevin Bahler, tr.8142a (Box 60)
  - Marsha Buck, tr.8143a (Box 60)
  - PFLAG, Jul. 17, 1990; tr.8144a (Box 60)
  - Friendship Messages, tr.8145a (Box 60)
  - Broadcast, March 3, 1998; tr.8146a (Box 60)
  - [unlabeled], tr.8147a (Box 60)
  - GLAAD: Harvey Fierstein, tr.8148a (Box 60)
  - PFLAG Taping for Bib Witeck, tr.8149a (Box 60)
  - Sandra Moore, Dallas radio, Apr. 1992; tr.8150a (Box 60)
  - Martin Adams, tr.8151a (Box 60)
  - Tulsa PFLAG, tr.8152a (Box 60)
  - Frechette, tr.8153a (Box 60)
  - Rev. Edward Townely, The Gay/Lesbian Spiritual Support Line, tr.8154a (Box 60)
  - [unlabeled], Sept. 26, 1999; tr.8155a (Box 60)
  - [unlabeled], tr.8156a (Box 60)
  - [unlabeled], tr.8157a (Box 60)
  - Perkins-Linden-Eldredge--Common Ground and Strategies--Colorado for Family Values, May 16, 1994; tr.8158a (Box 60)
  - When Parents Come Out: A Heartwarming Story--PFLAG National Convention, New Orleans, Sept. 5, 1993; tr.8159a (Box 60)
  - When Parents are "Out" More Than Their Kid--PFLAG National Convention, San Francisco, Sept. 3, 1994; tr.8160a (Box 60)
  - Fathers Only: Breaking the Code of Silence--PFLAG National Convention, San Francisco, Sept. 4, 1994; tr.8161a (Box 60)
  - Parents Coming out of the Closet as Parents: Getting up the Courage to Tell--PFLAG National Convention, San Francisco, Sept. 4, 1994; tr.8162a (Box 60)
  - I'm Bisexual and I Have Parents: Coming out to Our Families--PFLAG National Convention, San Francisco, Sept. 4, 1994; tr.8163a (Box 60)
  - [unlabeled], tr.8164a (Box 61)
  - Defamation, narrated by Harvey Fierstein--GLAAD, tr.8165a (Box 61)
  - Making Contact: Growing Up Gay, Jun. 4, 1997; tr.8166a (Box 61)
  - Policy vs. Paper Clips: More Insights on the Corporate Model for Your Nonprofit Board, 1989; tr.8167a (Box 61)
  - afternoon, Feb. 27, 1999; tr.8168a (Box 61)
  - [unlabeled], tr.8169a (Box 61)
  - PFLAG's Cultural Outreach Project--8th Creating Change--Detroit, Nov. 10-12, 1995; tr.8170a (Box 61)
  - Hill/Knowlton, PFLAG, Jul. 11, 1990; tr.8171a (Box 61)
  - Vicki Seirhik, tr.8172a (Box 61)
  - Mike Neubecker on "Christian" Talk Radio, Detroit, tr.8173a (Box 61)
  - Stonewall: Myth, Magic and Mobilization, Apr. 23, 1994; tr.8174a (Box 61)
  - PM, Feb. 27, 1999; tr.8175a (Box 61)
  - POM Radio Ad--San Diego, tr.8176a (Box 61)
  - PFLAG Dallas, tr.8177a (Box 61)
  - Kurt Olson, tr.8178a (Box 61)
  - The Family Heart: A Memoir of When Our Son Came Out--Robb Forman Dew--Cassette One, 1994; tr.8179a (Box 61)
  - The Family Heart: A Memoir of When Our Son Came Out--Robb Forman Dew--Cassette Two, 1994; tr.8180a (Box 61)
  - material written by Muriel Kirk (satire on relgious and conservatives), tr.8181a (Box 61)
  - Warm and Fuzzy Encounters: A Meeting of the Minds: Motivational Series for Meeting Planners, 1995; tr.8182a (Box 61)
  - An ill-informed Alan Howard, tr.8183a (Box 61)
  - Sept. 25, 1999, tr.8184a (Box 61)
  - Bev, Jul. 9, 1989; tr.8185a (Box 61)
  - Liza Minnelli--The Day After That--benefit for AmFAR, 1993; tr.8186a (Box 61)
  - 9AM, 10:15AM, Feb. 27, 1999; tr.8187a (Box 61)
  - Interactive Skills, Questions, tr.8188a (Box 61)
  - Bringing Truth to "Christian" Radio Audiences--Mike Neubecker, tr.8189a (Box 61)
  - "Innocent" (0:30); "Bashing" (0:30), 1995; V-375
  - "Straight from the Heart: Stories of parents' journeys to a new understanding of their lesbian and gay children" (23:54), 1994; V-376
  - "Love in Action: PFLAG's 15th Anniversary Retrospective" (17:12), 1996; V-699
  - "Lifetime: What Makes a Family", Jan. 22, 2001; V-828 (Box 62)
  - "TransFamily: PFLAG's Transgender Network", 2001; V-829 (Box 62)
  - "Shepardson Stern Kaminsky, PFLAG, Innocent, Bashing, Don't They Deserve It?, Torn Lives", V-830 (Box 62)
  - "Innocent," "Bashing", Oct. 26, 1995; V-831 (Box 62)
  - "Shepardson Stern Kaminsky, PFLAG, They Deserve It?", V-832 (Box 62)
  - "Voices of Vision: With Dignity for All: Celebrating Diversity", V-833 (Box 62)
  - "Project Open Mind PSAs: Innocent, Bashing, Don't They Deserve It?, Torn Lives (Shepardson Stern Kaminsky)", V-834 (Box 62)
  - "Love in Action: PFLAG's 15th Anniversary Retrospective", 1996; V-835 (Box 62)
  - "Family Photo", Nov. 1992; V-836 (Box 60)
  - "Straight from the Heart", March 9, 1995; V-837 (Box 60)
  - "Family Photo", Nov. 1992; V-838 (Box 61)
  - "Family Photo", Nov. 1992; V-839 (Box 61)
  - ABC-TV News - Charlotte, North Carolina, PFLAG, V-5433 (Box 68)
  - NIH: World News Tonight, Nightline, WJLA, June 1993; V-5434 (Box 68)
  - Project Open Mind Discussion (WA) - PFLAG Broadcast - (60:00), June 17, 1996; V-5435 (Box 68)
  - Teenage Sex Ed, Censorship, PFLAG, V-5436 (Box 68)
  - Part 1 Tulsa Library PFLAG Exhibits - Exhibit 1996, 1996; V-5437 (Box 68)
  - Part 2 Tulsa Library PFLAG Exhibits - The West R. Lib. 1997 (6-24-97), 1997; V-5438 (Box 68)
  - Part 3 Tulsa Library PFLAG Exhibits - Multicultural Resonance, V-5439 (Box 68)
  - Part 4 Tulsa Library PFLAG Exhibits - Lesbian and Gay Youth, Safe Schools, V-5440 (Box 68)
  - PFLAG Town Hall Meeting - Southern Methodist University, March 9, 2001; V-5441 (Box 68)
  - PFLAG Sacramento News Clips - Being Gay Today (6/99); Service of Remembrance (10/10/99); Love Won Out (11/6/99), 1999; V-5442 (Box 68)
  - Interviews with PFLAG members, no date, no title, chapter not ID-ed, n.d.; V-5443 (Box 68)
  - 30th Anniversary Video - PFLAG Fine Cut - TRT (10:19), January 6, 2004; V-5444 (Box 68)
- Series X. Media
  - G/L/B in politics, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - G/L/B in popular culture, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - G/L/B prominent personalities, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Religion/spirituality, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Religious right, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Spouses of G/L/B, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - State/municipal issues, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - G/L/B youth, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Civil liberties, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Gay events, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Abortion, 1989-1993 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - News clip- Paulette Goodman, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - Collected P-FLAG media releases, 1988-1991 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - News releases, 1992-1994 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - News release packet, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - Others' press releases, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Press releases, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - Press releases, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Misc. news clippings, 1990? (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - California press clippings, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - News articles posted online, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - News articles, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Media clips, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - Bernstein op-eds, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - News clips, 1991-1993 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - AIDS, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - History, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  - G/L/B marriage/unions, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  - G/L/B in the media, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  - G/L/B in the militarye, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  - Organizations, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  - Parents, families, friends of G/L/B, 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  - ROTC, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  - Misc. news clips, 1991-1999 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  - PFLAG press clip copies, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  - Misc. articles, 1988? (Box 39, Folder 57)
  - Bob Bernstein articles, 1988? (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - News clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - News clippings, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - News clippings, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - News clippings, 1990-1994 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - News clippings, 1991-1993 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - News clippings, 1991-1993 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Press releases/news clips, 1997-1999 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Press releases/news clips, 1990-1992 (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
  - PFLAG in the news, 1998-2001 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Press clips, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Press releases, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Press clippings, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Press clippings, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Press releases, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Press clippings, 2000 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Press clippings, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - GLBT misc., 1998 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - GLBT in the military, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - GLBT families (?), 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - HIV/AIDS, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Hate crimes, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Hate crimes, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Government pro-gay legislation, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Government anti-gay legislation, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - GLBT youth, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Education/schools, 1996-1999 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Misc. news clippings., 1997-1998 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Family articles, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Gay rights advocacy, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - GLBT misc., 1998 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - P-FLAG clippings, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - P-FLAG in the News, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Religious Right- conversion therapy, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Religious Right, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Religion- pro-gay, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - News clips, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - News clips, 1996-1999 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - News clips, 1994-1999 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - When Sons & Daughters are Gay, 1999 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Press Clippings, including Santorum, Gay Marriage, LGBT Rights, 1960s-1970s clippings on homosexuality, 1960s-2004 (Box 63, Folder 29-33)
  - National Press Clippings, 1990-1995 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - National Press Clippings, 1996-2000 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - National Press Clippings, 2001-2006 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - National Press Clippings, 2007 (Box 68, Folder 16-18)
  - National Press Clippings, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 19-20)
  - National Press Clippings, 2009 (Box 68, Folder 21)